yeah!break!care!break!
Đóng góp: hackpeace
Live your life, don't stop until it's done
Once you live for love then you've already won

When I look up through the infinite sky
I never thought that it could come to this
Just take my hand and together we'll fly
Let's go, I know, how high?

Soar above the clouds and see such beauty all around
This irreplaceable world needs us now
We have to join in the fight

Live your life like a KameHame-Ha
Give your all, don't ever give up!
When we're together, I know we can win
I have you to believe in!
Live your life, don't stop until it's done
Give your all, don't ever give up
All you need is love and to believe in yourself
It's easier when you believe