Dragon Soul (English)
Đóng góp: Danny Phantom
don't stop , don't stop we're look mow 
don't stop,there're so much to be found
we can find paradise
all we have to do is go go bring your soul
mystery about
made up and deep enegy (enegy)
ozon around
but I will no fear and free
I and these friends, you heard me loul that's how I live ( that's how I live)
I'm corage one thing
if no with me my enemy can never will
we will fight for love and no we
we will live to tell the story
there is nothing we can let you
nothing ever die ,we will ride for save
don't stop , don't stop we're look now
don't stop , keep your spirit pround
and right up on the wind
all we have to do is goooooo
don't stop, don't stop we're look now 
don't stop there's so much to be found
we can find paradise
all we have to do is go go bring your soul
DRAGON SOUL!!!!!!!!!!